VISHAL SAROCH

Masrer, jawala Mukhi, HP 176036 | +91-8219052310 | visalsharma.logic@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Organized and self-motivated software engineer graduate with 5+ years combined internship and professional experience. Fluent in Core PHP, Coodeigniter, Laraval SQL JavaScript, and CSS programming languages. Possess practical working knowledge of relational databases using Mysql. Constantly updating personal and professional technical skills with complementary collegiate courses and online bootcamps. Reliable and responsible team player.

Skills

- HTML
- CSS 3
- Javascript
- Bootstrap
- Jquery
- Ajax
- PHP

- Codeigniter 3
- Codeigniter 4
- Laravel

Work History

Realkeeper Technologies Pvt. Ltd

Oct 2017 - April 2020

Jr. PHP Developer

Rohni, New Delhi

- Programming and website development.
- Writing clean, scalable code.
- Developing PHP models.
- Teaching the Interns in the Academy.

RWN Digittech India Pvt. Ltd

June 2020 - July 2023

PHP Developer

Zrikpur, Punjab

- Develop, test and implement new software programs.
- Clearly and regularly communicate with management and technical support colleagues.
- Design and update software database. ...

 Test, maintain and recommend software improvements to ensure strong functionality and optimization.

AdelSocial Aug 2023 – Current

Sr. PHP Developer

Malvyanager, New Delhi

- Conducting analysis of website and application requirements.
- Writing back-end code and building efficient PHP modules.
- Developing back-end portals with an optimized database.
- Troubleshooting application and code issues.
- Integrating data storage solutions.
- Team management.

Education

10th Mar 2010

Himachal Pradesh Board Bharoli Kohala

12th Mar 2012

Himachal Pradesh Board Bharoli Kohala

BCA 2012-2015

HPU Shimla LIMIT Kathog